

**KEMAL FADY** 

Jl. Miad No.43 Kel. Kebayoran Baru Kec. Cipete Utara RT/RW 03/11 Jakarta Selatan 12150

(+62) 812 940 41747 faddyalkatiri@yahoo.com

# ABOUT ME

Few years of experience in Marketing, Public Relation and Business Management. Has a great understanding of Companies mission and vision. Strong analytical thinking person with great communication skills. A good time keeper who always enthusiastic to learn and undertake new challenges.

#### SKILLS

#### **WORK**

WINDOWS			
MACINTOSH			
PHOTOSHOP			
CORELDRAW			
MICROSOFT OFFICE			

#### **PERSONAL**

COMMUNICATION	
ORGANIZATION	
TEAM PLAYER	
CREATIVITY	
SOCIAL	

## **EXPERIENCE**

# CORPORATE SECRETARY JAKARTA FUTURES EXCHANGE (2011 - Present)

Act as a point of communication between the board of directors and company shareholders, reporting in a timely and accurate manner on company procedures and developments. Responsible for ensuring that an organization complies with standard financial and legal practice and maintains standards of corporate governance and responsible for the public relations initiatives within a company. Creates, manages, and implements PR campaigns with the goal of enriching a company's position within the public eye. Maintain strong relationships with government, media, and stakeholders.

## **EDUCATION**

MASTER OF BUSINESS MANAGEMENT BINUS UNIVERSITY (2012 - 2014)

BACHELOR OF ECONOMIC BINUS UNIVERSITY (2004 - 2008)

#### **VOLUNTEER**

#### DISASTER AND HUMANITARIAN RELIEF (December 2014)

Delivered aid from The Ministry of Trade, Commodity Futures Trading business communities in the Association of Indonesian Broker (ICMA) and the Association of Indonesian Derivatives Traders (IP2BI) to the flood victims in the District of Bale Endah District Bandung, West Java.

#### DISASTER AND HUMANITARIAN RELIEF (July 2013)

Delivered humanitarian aid for earthquake victims in the Bener Meriah Regency and Aceh Tengah Regency. This humanitarian aid was handed over symbolically by Mr. Gita Wirjawan, the Minister of Trade, to Mr. Zaini Abdullah, the Governor of Aceh, Ruslan Abdul Gani, the Regent of Bener Meriah Regency and Nasarudin, Regent of Aceh Tengah Regency.

## OTHER EXPERIENCE

#### JFX CENTER (2012 – Present)

Act as a Project Leader of JFX Center to be responsible for developing and maintaining marketing strategies to meet agreed company objectives, evaluate customer research, market conditions, competitor data and implement marketing plan alterations as needed and oversees all marketing, advertising and promotional staff and activities.

#### AIESEC INDONESIA (February 2012)

Act as a Committee from JFX for AIESEC Indonesia in "Social Entrepreneurship Action for Change". Managing all marketing for the company and activities within the marketing department. Developing the marketing strategy for the company in line with company objectives. Coordinating marketing campaigns with sales activities and overseeing the company's marketing budget. Creation and publication of all marketing material in line with marketing plans.

#### **SKILLS**

**LEGAL** 

SALES

MARKETING

RESEARCH

BUSINESS DEV.

FINANCE

PUBLIC RELATION

CORP. AFFAIRS

ITECHNOLOGY

OPERATION

#### GLOBAL RUBBER CONFERENCE (October 2013)

Act as a Delegate from JFX to planning and implementing promotional campaigns. Manage and improve lead generation campaigns, measuring results. Overall responsibility for brand management and corporate identity. Working closely with design agencies and assisting with new product launches. Maintain effective internal communications to ensure that all relevant company functions are kept informed of marketing objectives and analyzing potential strategic partner relationships for company marketing.

#### 9th Indonesian Palm Oil Conference (IPOC) (November 2013)

Act as a Delegate from JFX conduct market research to determine market requirements for existing and future products. Analysis of customer research, current market conditions and competitor information. Develop and implement marketing plans and projects for new and existing products. Expand and develop marketing platforms, manage the productivity of the marketing plans and projects. Monitor, review and report on all marketing activity result.

## ORGANIZATION EXPERIENCE

#### STELLAR INDONESIA (PROMOTER & EVENT ORGANIZER)

- The Launching of Eternal International in December 2011 at Ballroom, The Ritz Carlton Hotel, Jakarta
- The Launching of a IP Star (telecommunication company) in 15 Juli 2012 at Ballroom Hotel Hyatt Jakarta
- Yellow Submarine "New Year's Eve celebration" in 2011 2012 at Capocaccia, Pacific Place Jakarta
- Area 62 I festival musik Indonesia, May 2012 at Portico, Senayan City, Jakarta
- Area 62 II festival musik Indonesia, May 2012 at Summarecon Mall Serpong, Tangerang
- Area 62 III festival musik Indonesia, May 2012 at Ecopark, Ancol, Jakarta
- CIMB Has TALENT 2013, 8 10 November 2013 at XXI Ballroom, Djakarta Theatre, Jakarta
- An Evening Charity Gala "Children in Harmony" by Global Shapers Community Jakarta, 16 Juni 2014 at Grand Ballroom, Four Seasons Hotel, Kuningan, Jakarta
- BCA Indonesia Open 2014, 17 22 Juni 2014 at Istora Senayan, Jakarta
- HSBC Outing Jakarta Region #1 2014, 30 Oktober 2 November 2014, Yogyakarta
- 35 Tahun KFC Indonesia pada 20 Januari 2015 di Tennis Indoor, Senayan, Jakarta

## HYPERREAL MOVEMENT (CREATIVE AGENCY)

- Green Sands Weezer Concert 2013 January 8, 2013 at Lapangan D Senayan
- Green Sands Escape Session #1: Malang, Bromo, and Bali April 2013
- Green Sands Escape Session #2: Taman Nasional Berbak Jambi July 2013
- Green Sands Escape Session #3: Taman Nasional Tanjung Puting, Kalimantan October 2013
- Green Sands PL FAIR 2013: C.O.A.S.T January 26, 2013 at Parkir Timur Senayan
- Green Sands Grimes Concert 2013 March 16, 2013 at Gandaria City
- Green Sands Soulvibe 8th Anniversary 2013 March 28, 2013 at Usmar Ismail Concert Hall
- Green Sands "A curated market of all things cool" Brightspot Market 10, 7-10 November 2013 at Lotte Shopping Avenue
- NIKE "Ekin University" in April 14, 2015 at Green Andara, Jakarta

## JFX CENTER (LEARNING CENTER)

- PT Fasting Futures at Soegijapranata Semarang in September 12, 2013
- PT Kresna Futures at Universitas Kristen Indonesia in March 29, 2012
- PT Megah Tama Berjangka at Universitas Teknologi Jogjakarta in May 4, 2012
- PT Askap Futures at Universitas Lampung in June 28, 2012
- PT Monex Investindo Futures at Universitas Diponegoro in September 22, 2012
- PT Monex Investindo Futures at Institut Pertanian Bogor in July 12, 2012
- PT Agrodana Futures at Universitas Surabaya in October 6, 2012
- PT Rex Capital Futures at Universitas Kristen Satva Wacana in September 22, 2012
- PT Victory International at Universitas Ma Chung Malang in March 26, 2013
- PT Victory International at Sekolah Tinggi Ilmu Ekonomi Malangkucecwara in March 26, 2013
- PT Monex Investindo Futures at Universitas Janabadra Jogjakarta in October 9, 2013
- PT Victory International at Universitas Negeri Malang in November 14, 2013
- PT Victory International at Universitas Islam Negeri Sultan Syarif Kasim/UIN Suska (Pekanbaru Riau) in October 10, 2013
- PT Agrodana Futures at Politeknik Negeri Bandung in May 18, 2015
- PT Agrodana Futures at Universitas Katolik Widya Karya Malang in December 8, 2014